ATEFEH ETEMADIPOUR

JUNIOR UX DESIGNER

WITH FRONTEND COMPETENCE

CONTACT

+46793593574

Stockhom, Sweden

<u>Linkedin.com/in/atefeh-</u> etemadipour-bb575a158

https://github.com/Atefe1986

SKILLS

- Figma (Software)
- Build Wireframes and Low-Fidelity
 & High-Fidelity Prototypes
- · Usability Testing
- User Stories and User Personas
- User-centered Design
- HTML/CSS
- Javascript
- Miro Collaboration Platform
- Inkscape
- · Microsoft office MSP Microsoft
- Dynamics CRM

LANGUAGES

• English: Fluent

• Swedish: Limited Working

• Persian: Native

PROFILE SUMMARY

With a background in industrial engineering and more than 4 years of sales experience, I'm eager to work in the field of product design. As an industrial engineer, I gained knowledge about creating products, and as a salesperson in the software sector, I had many close relationships with customers. In order to accomplish my goal, I enrolled in a UX Design with Frontend competence course in Chas Academy and began learning about it. I'm so excited about the new techniques and tools I've discovered and I like to apply them in real life products.

WORK EXPERIENCE

 NOAVARAN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES GROUP IRAN, TEHRAN

Sales expert (Jun 2016 - Mar 2018)

Salesperson in the sale department, Extending the contract of organizations that are party to the contract and setting up the contract of new organizations Telephone support of organizations

 KIAN PARDAZ HOOSHMAND IRAN, TEHRAN

CRM specialist (Jun 2014 - Jun 2016)

CRM expert in the support and sale sector for Microsoft Dynamics CRM Customizing Microsoft dynamics CRM

EDUCATION

UX DESIGNER WITH FRONTEND COMPETENCE

- · Chas Academy, Stockholm, Sweden
- Current student
- Learning and developing skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, and user-centered design. Gaining expertise in UX design tools like Figma and usability-focused methodologies.

INDUSTRIAL ENGINEERING, BACHELOR(BSC/BA)

- Sadjad Institute of Higher Education, Khorasan Razavi, Iran 2004 -2009
- Project: Production Scheduling using Invasive Weed Optimization Algorithm, using Python

LICENCES & CERTIFICATIONS

- FOUNDATION OF USER EXPERIENCE (UX) DESIGN -COURSERA
- START THE UX DESIGN PROCESS: EMPATHIZE, DEFINE AND IDEATE - COURSERA
- BUILD WIREFRAMES AND LOW-FIDELITY PROTOTYPES -COURSERA
- CREATE HIGH-FIDELITY DESIGNS AND PROTOTYPES IN FIGMA CONDUCT UX RESEARCH AND TEST EARLY CONCEPTS - COURSERA
- PLANNING A CAREER IN USER EXPERIENCE LINKEDIN
- UX DESIGN: OVERVIEW LINKEDIN
- UX DESIGN: ANALYZING USER DATA LINKEDIN
- MSP INDUSTRILAL MANAGEMENT INSTITUTE IRAN-TEHRAN
- NETWORK+ CYBERTECH ACADEMY IRAN-TEHRAN